Inventory of the Richard Throssel Papers, 1900-1993 (bulk 1902-1933)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Photographs and Negatives, 1902-ca. 1920s; Series I.; 14.86 cubic ft. (6 letter boxes, 1 F24 box, 39 negative boxes, 5 shoe boxes and 4 F20 boxes).
  - 4 x 5 Glass Plate Negatives and Photographs, Subseries II.
    - Bathers - Camp in Background (Box 4, Folder 6)
      TP712
      Throssel #91
    - Riders along River (Box 4, Folder 6)
      TP713
      Throssel #92
    - Warriors Fording River (Box 4, Folder 7)
      TP714
      Throssel #93
    - Warriors Fording River (Box 4, Folder 7)
      TP714A
    - Riders Crossing River (Box 4, Folder 7)
      TP715
      Throssel #94
    - Camp Scene - Watering the Horses (Box 4, Folder 7)
      TP716
      Throssel #95
    - Branding (Box 4, Folder 7)
      TP717
      Throssel #97
    - "On the Trail" (Box 4, Folder 7)
      TP718
      Throssel ID #4505
      Throssel #99
    - Moving Horses (Box 4, Folder 7)
      TP719
      Throssel #100
    - Warriors Crossing River (Box 4, Folder 7)
      TP720
      Throssel #101
    - Water Carrier (Box 4, Folder 7)
      TP721
      Throssel #126
    - "Cheyenne - The Wood Gatherers" (Box 4, Folder 7)
      TP722
      Throssel #127
    - Two Men in Full Dress (Box 4, Folder 7)
      TP723
      Throssel #128
    - Woman (Box 4, Folder 8)
      TP724
      Throssel #129
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 8)
      TP725
      Throssel #130
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 8)
      TP726
      Throssel ID #452
      Throssel #131
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 8)
      TP727
      Throssel #132
    - "Cheyennes" - In Front of Thunderbird Tipi (Box 4, Folder 8)
      TP728
      Throssel #133
    - "The Open Door" (Box 4, Folder 8)
      TP729
      Throssel #134
    - Women Sitting Outside Tipi (Box 4, Folder 8)
      TP730
      Throssel #135
    - Women Picking Berries? (Box 4, Folder 8)
      TP731
      Throssel #136
    - Women Picking Berries? (Box 4, Folder 8)
      TP732
      Throssel #137
    - Man Painting the Sign of His Medicine - Camera in Foreground (Box 4, Folder 8)
      TP733
      Throssel #138
    - Man Painting the Sign of His Medicine - Camera in Foreground (Box 4, Folder 8)
      TP733A
    - Woman at Tipi Entrance (Box 4, Folder 9)
      TP734
      Throssel #139
    - "At Doorway" (Box 4, Folder 9)
      TP735
      Throssel ID #6814 11-1906
      Throssel #140
    - Woman Carrying Parcel (Box 4, Folder 9)
      TP736
      Throssel #141
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 9)
      TP737
      Throssel #142
    - Two Men in Full Dress (Box 4, Folder 9)
      TP738
      Throssel #143
    - Hikers (Box 4, Folder 9)
      TP739
      Throssel #144
    - Sweat Lodge (Box 4, Folder 9)
      TP740
      Throssel #145
    - Sweat Lodge (Box 4, Folder 9)
      TP741
      Throssel #146
    - "Crow Teepees" (Box 4, Folder 9)
      TP742
      Throssel #147
    - "Crow Teepees" (Box 4, Folder 9)
      TP743
      Throssel ID #486
      Throssel #148
    - Woman Carrying Wood by Thunderbird Tipi (Box 4, Folder 9)
      TP744
      Throssel #149
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP745
      Throssel #150
    - Sitting Outside Tipi (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP746
      Throssel #154
    - Basket Maker (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP747
    - Basket Maker (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP747A
    - Man and Dog Sitting Outside Tipi (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP748
    - Tree Burial (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP749
    - Horses (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP750
    - "On the Move" - Horses (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP751
      Throssel ID #463
    - "An Indian's Possessions" (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP752
      Throssel ID #431
    - "Going to Water" (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP753
      Throssel ID #432
    - Preparing Hide (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP754
      Throssel #192
    - Preparing Hide (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP755
      Throssel #195
    - Preparing Hide (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP756
    - Preparing Hide (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP757
      Throssel #196
    - Preparing Hide (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP758
      Throssel #197
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP759
      Throssel #198
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP760
      Throssel #199
    - Adult and Child Sitting on Hill Overlooking Village (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP761
      Throssel #200
    - Adult and Child Sitting on Hill Overlooking Village (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP762
      Throssel #201
    - Adult and Child Sitting on Hill Overlooking Village (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP763
      Throssel #202
    - Adult Sitting on Hill (Box 4, Folder 10)
      TP764
      Throssel #203
    - Shinny (Box 4, Folder 11)
      TP765
      Throssel #204
    - Shinny (Box 4, Folder 11)
      TP766
      Throssel #205
    - Shinny (Box 4, Folder 11)
      TP767
      Throssel #206
    - Shinny (Box 4, Folder 11)
      TP768
      Throssel #207
    - Shinny (Box 4, Folder 11)
      TP769
      Throssel #208
    - Shinny (Box 4, Folder 11)
      TP770
      Throssel #209
    - Shinny (Box 4, Folder 11)
      TP771
      Throssel #210
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP772
      Throssel #211
    - "The Start" (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP773
      Throssel ID #474
      Throssel #212
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP774
      Throssel #213
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP775
      Throssel #214
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP776
      Throssel #215
      1glass negative 4 x 5
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP777
      Throssel #216
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP778
      Throssel #217
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP779
      Throssel #218
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP780
      Throssel #219
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP781
      Throssel #220
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP782
      Throssel #221
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP783
      Throssel #222
    - Rodeo (Box 4, Folder 12)
      TP784
      Throssel ID #5485
      Throssel #223
    - "Watching the Races" (Box 4, Folder 13)
      TP785
      Throssel ID #475
      Throssel #224
    - Horse Races (Box 4, Folder 13)
      TP786
      Throssel #225
    - Horse Races (Box 4, Folder 13)
      TP787
      Throssel #226
    - "Old Buffalo Hunter's Race" (Box 4, Folder 13)
      TP788
      Throssel ID #4584
      Throssel #227
    - Horse Races (Box 4, Folder 13)
      TP789
      Throssel #228
    - Man Working Horse (Box 4, Folder 13)
      TP790
      Throssel #229
    - Man Working Horse (Box 4, Folder 13)
      TP791
      Throssel #230
    - Man on Horseback (Box 4, Folder 13)
      TP792
      AHC Neg. #19180
      Throssel #231
    - People in Grandstands (Box 4, Folder 13)
      TP793
      Throssel #232
    - Sun Dance - Cheyenne (Box 4, Folder 14)
      TP794
      Throssel #238
    - Woman Carrying Buffalo Skull Around Dance Tent - Sun Dance or Animal Dance (Box 4, Folder 14)
      TP795
      Throssel #239
    - "Raising the Dance Tent" (Box 4, Folder 14)
      TP796
      Throssel ID #464
      Throssel #240
    - Tobacco Dance Lodge (Box 4, Folder 14)
      TP797
      Throssel #241
    - "In the Dance Tent" (Box 4, Folder 14)
      TP798
      Throssel #242
    - Spectators (Box 4, Folder 14)
      TP799
      AHC Neg. #19181
      Throssel #243
    - Interior of Dance Tent (Box 4, Folder 14)
      TP800
      Throssel #244
    - "In the Dance Tent" (Box 4, Folder 14)
      TP801
      Throssel ID #421, 1905
      Throssel #245
    - Dance (Box 4, Folder 14)
      TP802
      Throssel #271
    - Raising Sun Pole? (Box 4, Folder 14)
      TP803
      Throssel #272
    - Preparing Sun Pole? (Box 4, Folder 15)
      TP804
      Throssel #273
    - Preparing Sun Pole? (Box 4, Folder 15)
      TP805
      Throssel #274
    - Dancers (Box 4, Folder 15)
      TP806
      Negative Box 42
      Throssel #275
    - Dancers (Box 4, Folder 15)
      TP807
    - Preparing Sun Pole? (Box 4, Folder 15)
      TP808
    - Dancer (Box 4, Folder 15)
      TP809
      Throssel #271A
    - Dancing (Box 4, Folder 15)
      TP810
      Throssel #272A
    - Dancing (Box 4, Folder 15)
      TP811
      Throssel #273A
    - "Part of a Sundance" - "Caravan Dance"? (Box 4, Folder 15)
      TP812
      Throssel ID #6823, 11-1906
      Throssel #274A
    - Dancers (Box 4, Folder 15)
      TP813
      Throssel #275A
    - Dancers (Box 4, Folder 16)
      TP814
      Throssel #276A
    - Preparing Sun Pole (Box 4, Folder 16)
      TP815
      Throssel #278A
    - Dancers (Box 4, Folder 16)
      TP816
      Throssel #279A
    - Sun Dance (Box 4, Folder 16)
      TP817
      Throssel #329
    - Dance (Box 4, Folder 16)
      TP818
      Throssel #330
    - Dance (Box 4, Folder 16)
      TP819
      Throssel #331
    - Dance - Non-Indian in Foreground (Box 4, Folder 16)
      TP820
      Throssel #332
    - Dance (Box 4, Folder 16)
      TP821
      Throssel #333
    - Animal Dance[?] (Box 4, Folder 16)
      TP822
      Throssel #334
    - Dance (Box 4, Folder 16)
      TP823
      Throssel #335
    - Dance (Box 4, Folder 17)
      TP824
      Throssel #336
    - Men on Horses (Box 4, Folder 17)
      TP825
      Throssel #337
    - Men on Horses - Back View (Box 4, Folder 17)
      TP826
      Throssel #338
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 17)
      TP827
      Throssel #339
    - Rider in Full Dress (Box 4, Folder 17)
      TP828
      Throssel #340
    - Rider (Box 4, Folder 17)
      TP829
      Throssel #341
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 17)
      TP830
      Throssel #343
    - "Driving in the Horses" (Box 4, Folder 17)
      TP831
      AHC Neg. #19464
      Throssel ID #6822
      Throssel #344
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 17)
      TP832
      Throssel #345
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 17)
      TP833
      Throssel #346
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 18)
      TP834
      Throssel #347
    - Rider - Dismounted (Box 4, Folder 18)
      TP835
      Throssel #348
    - Riders with U.S. Flag (Box 4, Folder 18)
      TP836
      AHC Neg. #19647
      Throssel #349
    - Women Riders (Box 4, Folder 18)
      TP837
      Throssel #350
    - Women Riders (Box 4, Folder 18)
      TP838
      Throssel #351
    - "Old Timers" (Box 4, Folder 18)
      TP839
      Throssel ID #480
      Throssel #352
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 18)
      TP840
      Throssel #353
    - "Old Timers Parading" (Box 4, Folder 18)
      TP841
      AHC Neg. #19155
      Throssel ID #486, 1906
      Throssel #354
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 18)
      TP842
      Throssel #355
    - "The Leaders" (Box 4, Folder 18)
      TP843
      Throssel ID #6829, 11-06
      Throssel #356
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 18)
      TP844
      Throssel #357
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP845
      Throssel #358
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP846
      AHC Neg. #19255
      Throssel #359
    - Processions of Riders (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP847
      Throssel #360
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP848
      Throssel #361
    - Riders in Formation (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP849
      Throssel #362
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP850
      Throssel #363
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP851
      Throssel #364
    - Riders - Reenactment (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP852
      Throssel #365
    - Reenactment (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP853
      Throssel #366
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP854
      Throssel #367
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP855
      Throssel #368
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 19)
      TP856
      Throssel #369
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 20)
      TP857
      Throssel #370
    - Women Riders (Box 4, Folder 20)
      TP858
      Throssel #371
    - "The Rustler" (Box 4, Folder 20)
      TP859
      Throssel ID #4510
      Throssel #372
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 20)
      TP860
      Throssel #373
    - Riders Crossing River - Cameraman Present (Box 4, Folder 20)
      TP861
      Throssel #374
    - Riders in Full Dress (Box 4, Folder 20)
      TP862
      Throssel #375
    - Riders in Formation (Box 4, Folder 20)
      TP863
      Throssel #376
    - "On Parade" (Box 4, Folder 20)
      TP864
      Throssel ID #6835
      Throssel #377
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 20)
      TP865
      Throssel #378
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 20)
      TP866
      Throssel #379
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 20)
      TP867
      Throssel #380
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 21)
      TP868
      Throssel #381
    - "The Returning Riders" (Box 4, Folder 21)
      TP869
      AHC Neg. #19154
      Throssel #382
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 21)
      TP870
      Throssel #383
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 21)
      TP871
      Throssel #384
    - Rider (Box 4, Folder 21)
      TP872
      Throssel #385
    - Riders - One with Drum (Box 4, Folder 21)
      TP873
      Throssel #386
    - "In Full Dress" (Box 4, Folder 21)
      TP874
      AHC Neg. #19645
      Throssel ID #1906
      Throssel #387
    - Riders in Full Dress (Box 4, Folder 21)
      TP875
      Throssel #388
    - Riders in Formation (Box 4, Folder 21)
      TP876
      Throssel #389
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 21)
      TP877
      Throssel #390
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 21)
      TP878
      Throssel #391
    - Rider with Eagle Flag (Box 4, Folder 22)
      TP879
      Throssel #392
    - "The Wanderers" with U.S. Flag" (Box 4, Folder 22)
      TP880
      Throssel #393
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 22)
      TP881
      Throssel #394
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 22)
      TP882
      Throssel #395
    - Battle Reenactment (Box 4, Folder 22)
      TP883
      Throssel #396
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 22)
      TP884
      Throssel #397
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 22)
      TP885
      Throssel #398
    - Reenactment (Box 4, Folder 22)
      TP886
      Throssel #399
    - Reenactment (Box 4, Folder 22)
      TP887
      Throssel #400
    - Riding Through Brush (Box 4, Folder 22)
      TP888
      Throssel #401
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 23)
      TP889
      Throssel #402
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 23)
      TP890
      Throssel #403
    - Riders with Willow Boughs (Box 4, Folder 23)
      TP891
      Throssel #404
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 23)
      TP892
      Throssel #405
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 23)
      TP893
      Throssel #406
    - Reenactment? (Box 4, Folder 23)
      TP894
      Throssel #407
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 23)
      TP895
      Throssel #408
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 23)
      TP896
      Throssel #409
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 23)
      TP897
      Throssel #410
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 23)
      TP898
      Throssel #411
    - Riders (Box 4, Folder 23)
      TP899
      AHC Neg. #19648
      Throssel #412
    - Reenactment? (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP900
      Throssel #413
    - Riders Pulling Something - Possibly Tent Poles (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP901
      Throssel #414
    - "The Advance Scouts" (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP902
      Throssel #415
    - Riders - Reenactment (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP903
      Throssel #418
    - Riders - Reenactment (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP904
      Throssel #419
    - Riders - Reenactment (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP905
      Throssel #420
    - "Winner of the Buffalo Hunter's Race" (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP906
      Throssel #716
    - Child (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP907
      AHC Neg. #15657
      Throssel #717
    - Girl in Front of Tipi (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP908
      Throssel #718
    - Girl with Puppy (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP909
      Throssel #719
    - Woman with Two Children (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP910
      Throssel #720
    - Woman with Two Children (Box 4, Folder 24)
      TP910A
    - Mother and Baby (Box 4, Folder 25)
      TP911
      AHC Neg. #15666
      Throssel #458
    - Baby in Cradle Board (Box 4, Folder 25)
      TP912
      AHC Neg. #15659
      Throssel #459
    - "Blanket Bull's Daughter" (Box 4, Folder 25)
      TP913
      AHC Neg. #15658
      Throssel #460
    - "Sings to Man" (Box 4, Folder 25)
      TP914
      Throssel #461
    - "Mrs. Angela Blackhawk" - Crow (Box 4, Folder 25)
      TP915
      Throssel #475
    - Frank S.? Portrait (Box 4, Folder 25)
      TP916
      Throssel #601
    - Man - Unidentified - Portrait (Box 4, Folder 25)
      TP917
      Throssel #602
    - "Crow Warrior" (Box 4, Folder 25)
      TP918
      Throssel ID #4507, 482 1904
      Throssel #603
    - Man Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 25)
      TP919
      Throssel #648
    - Sitting Bull (Box 4, Folder 25)
      TP920
      Throssel #649
    - Raising a Tipi (Box 4, Folder 26)
      TP921
      Throssel #786
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 26)
      TP922
      Throssel #787
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 26)
      TP923
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 26)
      TP924
      Throssel #789
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 26)
      TP925
    - Ceremonial Tipi (Box 4, Folder 26)
      TP926
      Throssel #790
    - Ceremonial Tipi (Box 4, Folder 26)
      TP927
      Throssel #791
    - Tipi Frame - Winter (Box 4, Folder 26)
      TP928
      Throssel #792
    - Tipi Frame and Willow Structures - Winter (Box 4, Folder 27)
      TP929
      Throssel #793
    - Tipi Frame, Wagons, Belongings (Box 4, Folder 27)
      TP930
      Throssel #794
    - Crow Ceremonial Lodge (Box 4, Folder 27)
      TP931
      Throssel #795
    - Tipis by River (Box 4, Folder 27)
      TP932
      Throssel #800
    - Winter Camp (Box 4, Folder 27)
      TP933
      AHC Neg. #15653
      Throssel #801
    - Camp by River (Box 4, Folder 27)
      TP934
      Throssel #802
    - Village Scene (Box 4, Folder 27)
      TP935
      Throssel #803
    - Village Scene (Box 4, Folder 27)
      TP936
      Throssel #804
    - Camp by River (Box 4, Folder 27)
      TP937
      Throssel #805
    - Camp by River (Box 4, Folder 27)
      TP938
      Throssel #806
    - Fording River - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP939
      Throssel #807
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP940
      Negative Box 43
      Throssel #808
    - "Camp Life" (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP941
      Throssel ID #467
      Throssel #809
    - Camp by River (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP942
      Throssel #810
    - "The Camp Beyond" (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP943
      Throssel #811
    - "The Camp Beyond" - Tipi Poles Stacked Up (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP944
      Throssel #812
    - Camp by River (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP945
      Throssel #813
    - Village Scene (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP946
      Throssel #814
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP947
      Throssel #815
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP948
      Throssel #816
    - Village (Box 4, Folder 29)
      TP949
      Throssel #817
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 29)
      TP950
      Throssel #818
    - Camp by River (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP951
    - "The Home of Man" (Box 4, Folder 28)
      TP952
    - "The Home of Man," Tipi in winter (Box 4, Folder 29)
      TP953
      Throssel #880
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 29)
      TP954
      Throssel #881
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 29)
      TP955
      Throssel #882
    - Tipi with War Bonnet Outside (Box 4, Folder 29)
      TP956
      Throssel #883
    - Tipi with War Bonnet Outside (Box 4, Folder 29)
      TP957
      Throssel #884
    - Tipi and Horse (Box 4, Folder 29)
      TP958
      Throssel #885
    - "An Evening Tipi" (Box 4, Folder 29)
      TP959
      Throssel ID #4501
      Throssel #886
    - Medicine Tipi (Box 4, Folder 29)
      TP960
      Throssel #887
    - Camp Scene - Tipi, Sweat Lodge, Cooking Equipment (Box 4, Folder 30)
      TP961
      AHC Neg. #19254
      Throssel #888
    - Ceremonial Lodge and Sweat Lodge (Box 4, Folder 30)
      TP962
      Throssel #889
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 30)
      TP963
      Throssel #890
    - Tipi by River (Box 4, Folder 30)
      TP964
      Throssel #891
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 30)
      TP965
      Throssel #892
    - "A Cheyenne Home" (Box 4, Folder 30)
      TP966
      Throssel ID #468
      Throssel #893
    - Blackfoot Lodge (Box 4, Folder 30)
      TP967
      Throssel #894
    - Painted Tipi (Box 4, Folder 30)
      TP968
      Throssel #895
    - Blackfoot Lodge (Box 4, Folder 30)
      TP969
      Throssel #896
    - "Wounded Elk's Tipi" (Box 4, Folder 30)
      TP970
      Throssel #897
    - Tipi (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP971
      Throssel #898
    - Camp Scene (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP972
      Throssel #899
    - Tipi (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP973
      Throssel #900
    - Painted Tipi (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP974
    - Painted Tipi (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP975
    - Camp Scene (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP976
      Throssel ID #8V004 "©" 1904
    - "Deserted" (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP977
    - "Covering the Poles" (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP978
      Throssel #932
    - "Covering the Poles" (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP978A
    - Woman Chopping Wood (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP979
      Throssel #933
    - Raising a Tipi (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP980
      Throssel #934
    - Tipis - One with Thunderbird (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP981
      Throssel #935
    - Tipis by River (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP982
      Throssel #936
    - Tipis by River (Box 5, Folder 1)
      TP983
      Throssel #937
    - Painted Tipi - Detail (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP984
      Throssel #938
    - Tipi (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP985
      Throssel #939
    - Camp by River (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP986
      Throssel #941
    - Camp Scene (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP987
    - "In their Native Wildwood" (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP988
      Throssel ID #462
      Throssel #958
    - Men in Full Dress - Posed (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP989
      Throssel #959
    - Event (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP 989A
    - Event (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP990
      Throssel #963
    - Watching the Tobacco Dance (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP991
      Throssel #964
    - Men Carrying Large Drum (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP992
      Throssel #965
    - Ceremony (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP993
      Throssel #966
    - Person Running (Box 5, Folder 2)
      TP994
      Throssel #967
    - Dance (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP995
      Throssel #969
    - Camp by River (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP996
      Throssel #985
    - Camp Scene (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP997
      Throssel #986
    - Camp Scene (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP998
      Throssel #987
    - Painted Tipi (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP999
      Throssel #988
    - Camp Scene (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP1000
      Throssel #989
    - Sweat Lodge (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP1001
    - Sweat Lodge (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP1002
    - Sweat Lodge (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP1003
    - Sweat Lodge (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP1004
    - Man Walking on Road - Horses and Cabin in Background (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP1005
      Throssel #961
    - Man in Suit Between Indian Boy and Woman - Tipi in Background (Box 5, Folder 3)
      TP1006
    - Two Indians Standing Near Tipi - Horse in Foreground (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1007
    - Two Indian Riders Overlooking an Indian Camp Located in a Valley (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1008
    - Woman Carrying a Bundle of Wood on her Back (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1009
    - View of an Indian Camp Near River (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1010
    - Woman Bent Over Working (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1011
    - Man Leading Horse (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1012
    - Two Horses - Indian Camp in Background (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1013
    - Two Horses in Front of Tipi (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1014
    - Driving Horses to River (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1015
    - Two Men Packing Gear on to Horse (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1016
    - Three Men with Horses Near Rocky Stream (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1017
      1 celluloid negative 2½ x 5
    - Man Riding Horseback While Leading Packhorse (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1018
      Negative Box 44
      1 celluloid negative 3½ x 5½
    - Man Riding Horseback While Leading (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1018A
    - Men on Horseback - Back View (Box 5, Folder 4)